Glory to Ukraine, we are volunteers of Podillia again in the fund.
Слава Украине мы снова в фонде волонтеры
And this means that today there is an
А это значит сегодня идет какая-то
awesome shipment to the front, and you
офигенная отправочка на фронт и это вы
don't even know what it is. And these are seven
даже не представляете что это А это семь
devices that will allow you to detect
устройств, которые будут позволять обнаруживать
enemy drones, look through their eyes,
вражеские fподроны смотреть их глазами
that is, see the same thing that the oat org sees,
то есть видеть то же, что видит оat org
find the place of takeoff  The landing place of
находить место взльта Место посадки ты
these drones, identify the place from where they
эти дроны обнаруживать место откуда они
took off, direct artillery there,
вылетали наводить туда артиллерию
direct our drones there, and make
наводить туда наши дроны и делать
very, very many black bags, and
очень много черных пакетов а в
this black case will help with this,
этому помогут вот этот черный
in which these beautiful products will be
кейс в котором будут эти красивые изделия
moved. For the convenience of our guys,
передвигаться Для удобства наших ребят
they will be on such a TV
на таком телевизоре они будут
while sipping coffee, contemplate and analyze
попивая кофе созерцать и анализировать
where it is flying from, and then throw the drone
откуда вылетает Та падла бросать его Дрон
to the ground so that it does not reach our
на землю чтобы он не долетел до наших
positions and does not harm anyone, and
позиций и не плохо не повредил никого и
direct artillery or other
приводить артиллерию или других операторов
drone operators to this rat's nest, a huge
Дронов на это крысиное гнездо огромно
thank you to everyone who informed all subscribers of the
благодарность всем кто донать всем подписчикам
channel from Ukraine and other  countries yes
канала из Украины из других стран да
Huge thanks to everyone from other countries
Большое спасибо всем из других стран
who support the armed forces of Ukraine
кто поддерживает вооружённые силы Украины
who will donate to our gatherings. As you can see,
кто донатит на сборы Как Вы видите
they materialize into very important things
они материализовыются в очень еные Вещи
that help save the lives of our
которые помогают сохранить жизни наших
children and de-
ребят и сделать
Nazify those who have crept into our
денацификацию тех, кто прилез на нашу
territory. Glory to Ukraine, support the Armed Forces
территорию Слава Украине поддерживайте ВСУ